https://www.starting-a-personal-training-business.com/privacy-policy.html

Select LanguageAfrikaansAlbanianArabicArmenianAzerbaijaniBasqueBelarusianBulgarianCatalanChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CroatianCzechDanishDutchEnglishEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchGalicianGeorgianGermanGreekHaitian CreoleHebrewHindiHungarianIcelandicIndonesianIrishItalianJapaneseKoreanLatvianLithuanianMacedonianMalayMalteseNorwegianPersianPolishPortugueseRomanianRussianSerbianSlovakSlovenianSpanishSwahiliSwedishThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduVietnameseWelshYiddish
Step 1:
Is Personal Training
Right for Me?
Step 2:
Get Certified
Step 3:
Get the Job
Step 4:
Launch Your Business
Step 5:
Train Smarter
- Popular Pages -
Exam Prep Course
Complete Training System
Business Plan
List of PT Schools
Cert Comparison
Cert Discounts
Privacy and Site Policies
We do not sell any personal information to third parties.
We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types
of personal information we receive and collect when you use
this web site, as well as some of the steps we take to
safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision
about sharing personal information with us.
This web site strives to maintain the highest standards of
decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are
dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy
on our website.
Personal Information
This web site collects personally identifiable information
from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information
collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address,
company name and telephone number.
This information is collected if you request information from us, participate
in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some
other service or information from us. The information collected is internally
reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of
updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.
Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we
make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information
we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information
received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not
be sold or provided to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies
are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your
Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a
cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For
example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's
services, a cookie enables this web site to recall your
specific information on subsequent visits.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web
browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully
experience the interactive features of the site.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our
website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address,
email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites
in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to
you.
In addition, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads to
our site. Google's use of the Dart cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors
based on visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Visitors may opt
out of the Dart cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network
privacy policy.
Google may use interest based advertising where they recognize the types of
webpages users visit across the Adsense network.This helps advertisers reach
users on the basis of their interests.
Search Box
The search box on this web site ("Search Box") is powered by Google Inc
("Google"). You acknowledge and agree that Google's privacy policy (located at http://www.google.com/privacy.html)
shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you
consent to Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy
policy.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the
age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy
Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from
anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal Information
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally
identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users,
to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the
site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The
information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with
other organizations for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If this web site is sold, the information we have obtained
from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the
new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you
may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that
change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure
that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to
protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information
through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or
would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us
page.
Updates and Effective Date
This web site reserves the right to make changes in this
policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will
know what information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to this web site's Privacy Policy as
posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered
by this site.
Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
Disclosures
This site is my personal site. It accepts advertising and other forms of compensation. Such compensation does not influence the information in this site. We always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences. "Ads by Google" are not selected by me, so if you see a Google ad and a Web page about the same product or service, it is a coincidence. I only accept non-Google sponsorships from providers of high-quality goods or services. I appreciate their recognition and support of this site. Rest assured that the actual content on sponsored pages are independent of any sponsorship or affiliate relationship. Please do support my sponsors and recommendations. This site takes time and effort to deliver original content, free, to you. Supporting my sponsors is a WIN-WIN-WIN for you, me, and them. Thank you very much.
Discussion Forum Guidelines
Any submission to this site must be original (not copied), in good taste, legal, accurate and true, non-defamatory, non-threatening, non-confidential, non-infringing of copyrights owned by others and relevant for this site. Please do not enter HTML (it will be converted to text) or ALL CAPS (they will be converted to lower case). Posts should be non-commercial/non-promotional in nature and not contain commercial web addresses, e-mail addresses or phone numbers. Starting-a-personal-training-business.com reserves the right to reject or edit or delete any parts that violate the above, including the right to ban offenders from submitting again. You must certify that you have the right to submit the text and photo prior to submitting. Your submission signifies agreement to the above and that you agree to grant an exclusive, royalty-free, irrevocable, transferable, perpetual license to publicly display the submission on this Web site only. I also grant Starting-a-personal-training-business.com the right to pursue anyone who copies my submission.
Home | Sitemap | Contact | Support
Our Site | Trainer
Directory | Discussion
Forum | What's New | Privacy
Step
1: Is Personal Training Right for Me? | Step
2: Get Certified |
Step 3
Personal Training Business. All rights reserved. We do not sell any information to third parties.
